<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Delhi Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="nav_header">Delhi Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="nav_item1">Places</string>
    <string name="nav_item2">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="nav_item3">Hotels</string>
    <string name="nav_item4">Festivals &amp; Events</string>
    <string name="place1">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="place1_description">The Red Fort is a historic fort.  It is located in the center of Delhi and houses a number of museums. In addition to accommodating the emperors and their households, it was the ceremonial and political center of the Mughal state and the setting for events critically impacting the region.</string>
    <string name="place2">Qutb Minar</string>
    <string name="place2_description">The Qutub Minar is a minaret that forms a part of the Qutab complex, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Mehrauli area. It is a 73-metre (239.5 feet) tall tapering tower of five storeys, with a 14.3 metres (47 feet) base diameter, reducing to 2.7 metres (9 feet) at the peak. It contains a spiral staircase of 379 steps.</string>
    <string name="place3">India Gate</string>
    <string name="place3_description">The India Gate (originally called the All India War Memorial) is a war memorial located astride the Rajpath. India Gate is a memorial to 70,000 soldiers of the Indian Army who died in the period 1914–21. 13,300 servicemen\'s names are inscribed on the gate.</string>
    <string name="place4">Lotus Temple</string>
    <string name="place4_description">The Lotus Temple is a House of Worship that was dedicated in December 1986, costing $10 million.It has flower-like shape.It is is open to all, regardless of religion or any other qualification. The building is composed of 27 free-standing marble-clad "petals" arranged in clusters of three to form nine sides with a height of slightly over 40 metres and a capacity of 2,500 people.</string>
    <string name="place5">Jama Masjid</string>
    <string name="place5_description">It is one of the largest mosques in India. It was built by Mughal emperor Shah Jahan between 1644 and 1656 at a cost of 1 million rupees, and was inaugurated by an imam from Bukhara, present-day Uzbekistan. The mosque was completed in 1656 AD with three great gates, four towers and two 40 m high minarets constructed of strips of red sandstone and white marble. The courtyard can accommodate more than 25,000 people.</string>
    <string name="place6">Chandni Chowk</string>
    <string name="place6_description">The Chandni Chowk is one of the oldest and busiest markets. It is located close to Old Delhi Railway Station. The Red Fort monument is located within the market. It was built in the 17th century by Mughal Emperor of India Shah Jahan and designed by his daughter Jahanara. The market was once divided by canals to reflect moonlight and remains one of India\'s largest wholesale markets.</string>
    <string name="restaurant1">The Rose Café</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_description">This cosy Victorian-style cafe offers light meals and freshly prepared desserts. The location and ambience of this place make you feel like you’re having food in some sleepy town in a European country.\n\nCost For Two: Rs. 1,300\n\nAddress: Saket, Delhi</string>
    <string name="restaurant2">Sevilla – The Claridges</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_description">If you’re willing to splash some cash, then Sevilla has the perfect setting for a romantic date. The interiors are beautifully done to capture the essence of Spain.\n\nCost For Two: Rs. 4,500\n\nAddress: Aurangzeb Road, Delhi</string>
    <string name="restaurant3">The Big Yellow Door</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_description">This gem of a place is great for hanging out with your buddies over delicious pastas and burgers. The ambience will transport you to a different world, away from the chaos of Delhi.\n\nCost For Two: Rs. 600\n\nAddress: Satyaniketan, Delhi</string>
    <string name="restaurant4">Beeryani</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_description">A small place located in the heart of the SDA market near IIT, this joint is popular amongst students as it supplies them with the only two things they desire in life – Beer and Biryani.\n\nCost For Two: Rs. 700\n\nAddress: SDA, Delhi</string>
    <string name="restaurant5">Bukhara</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_description">Bukhara has been voted amongst the best restaurants in Asia, and for a good reason. The Dhaba-like ambience and the absence of cutlery ensure that you get a truly Indian eating experience.\n\nCost For Two: Rs. 6,500\n\nAddress: Chanakyapuri, Delhi</string>
    <string name="restaurant6">Masala Library</string>
    <string name="restaurant6_description">This classy, swanky restaurant impresses with its grandiose decor, top notch service and heavenly grub.\n\nCost For Two: Rs. 5,000\n\nAddress: Janpath, Delhi</string>
    <string name="festival1">Republic Day</string>
    <string name="festival1_description">Republic Day is observed on 26 January every year with the feel of patriotism in the hearts of the citizens. The day is marked with parade, various stunts and displays by Indian Armed Forces, cultural performances by artists from different regions of India and floats.</string>
    <string name="festival2">Book Fair</string>
    <string name="festival2_description">Delhi organizes World Book Fair at Pragati Maidan in the month of February every year. It receives numerous participants and visitors from all over the world. This fair promotes Indian publishers and India’s Literature throughout the world.</string>
    <string name="festival3">Flower Show</string>
    <string name="festival3_description">The Delhi Flower Show is organized in Purana Quila, in the month of February. It is the greatest flower exhibition held in India showcasing a range of colorful and exotic flowers. It is an important event of Delhi. </string>
    <string name="festival4">International Mango Festival</string>
    <string name="festival4_description">This festival is celebrated in Talkatora Stadium in the month of July, displaying more than 500 types of mangoes. Visitors can taste mangoes for free.</string>
    <string name="festival5">Holi</string>
    <string name="festival5_description">The festival of colors, Holi is celebrated in Delhi with much enthusiasm. On this day, faces smeared with vibrant colors can be seen on the roads and lanes of Delhi. This festival is marked with enjoyment and sweet treats.</string>
    <string name="festival6">Diwali</string>
    <string name="festival6_description">The festival of lights is celebrated with splendor and enthusiasm in the capital city. Diwali signifies the return of Lord Rama to Ayodhya. People illuminate their homes, shops and streets. Sweets and gifts are exchanged as gesture of love.</string>
    <string name="hotel1">The JRD Luxury Boutique Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel1_description">Located in the Safdarjung Enclave neighborhood in New Delhi, 7 miles from Raj Ghat, The JRD Luxury Boutique Hotel features air-conditioned rooms with free WiFi throughout the property.</string>
    <string name="hotel2">Hotel Amaltas International</string>Svelte Hotel and Personal Suite
    <string name="hotel2_description">Featuring free WiFi, Hotel Amaltas International offers accommodations in New Delhi. Free private parking is available on site.</string>
    <string name="hotel3">The Ashok Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel3_description">Located in New Delhi, 5 miles from Raj Ghat, The Ashok, New Delhi features a seasonal outdoor pool and views of the pool. Guests can enjoy the on-site restaurant. </string>
    <string name="hotel4">Hotel JRD Exotica</string>
    <string name="hotel4_description">Located in New Delhi, 7 miles from Raj Ghat, Hotel JRD Exotica features a restaurant and free WiFi throughout the property. Free private parking is available on site. </string>
    <string name="hotel5">Svelte Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel5_description">Inside Select Citywalk Shopping Mall, a short walk from dining and entertainment options, Svelte Hotel and Personal Suite offers well-furnished suites with kitchenettes.</string>
    <string name="hotel6">Hotel Samrat</string>
    <string name="hotel6_description">Featuring free WiFi, a fitness center and an outdoor pool, Hotel Samrat offers accommodations in New Delhi. Guests can enjoy the on-site bar. All rooms come with a flat-screen TV with cable channels.</string>
</resources>